<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Industries on inomial</title>
    <link>/industries/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Industries on inomial</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 12:48:56 +0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/industries/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Other Industries &#43; Smile Software</title>
      <link>/industries/other-industries/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 12:48:56 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/industries/other-industries/</guid>
      <description>If you have an automatic billing or service management need Inomial may be able to help. Smile’s incredibly flexible design allows it to be relevant to more than telecommunication or ISP applications. Smile software can be readily adapted to support many automated billing needs, such as content providers and serviced officers. Smile is only limited by your imagination.
Contact Inomial to discuss your requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media &#43; Smile Software</title>
      <link>/industries/media/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 12:46:26 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/industries/media/</guid>
      <description>As media delivery methods evolve, so to must your automated billing. Whether you deliver content based on a static subscription billing method or using an on-demand approach, Inomial’s flexible APIs let you determine the charging models that works best for you. Build your customer base, simplify your ordering, billing and invoicing process, and make the most of your revenue. With Smile software your automatic billing capabilities are virtually unlimited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV &#43; Smile Software</title>
      <link>/industries/tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 12:39:06 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/industries/tv/</guid>
      <description>Inomial’s Smile software and extensive automatic billing and service management experience is well suited to IPTV, DOCSIS, cable and satellite TV markets, providing subscription automation and Video on Demand (VoD) services.
Inomial’s high performance, highly available, distributed APIs can be integrated with existing TV systems and content networks to enable complete, resilient end-to-end billing functionality. Managed services include ordering, VoD, billing and invoicing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telecommunications &#43; Smile Software</title>
      <link>/industries/telecommunications/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 12:29:05 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/industries/telecommunications/</guid>
      <description>Inomial has been partnering with the telecommunications industry for over 15 years. As telecommunication requirements have grown broader and more complex, so has Smile software grown into a full-featured, flexible automated billing and service management solution.
The telecommunications industry is an ever-transforming environment, with the introduction of new access technologies, consumer devices, services, payment methods and content. Inomial’s automatic billing and service management system is flexible enough to handle multiple offerings and changes at an escalating rate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISP &#43; Smile Software</title>
      <link>/industries/isp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 10:49:16 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/industries/isp/</guid>
      <description> In a highly aggressive ISP environment, Inomial knows you have to stay competitive to survive. Inomial’s automated billing and service management solution plays a big part in saving you time and money.
Smile’s flexibility allows you to deliver creative feature-rich packages quickly. Match or surpass your competitors offerings, with Smile software re-calculating charges automatically.
Increase your revenue, reduce your costs and improve the customer experience.
ISP carrier types include:  Retail Wholesale WiFi  ISP service types include:  DSL Wireless WiFI  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Industries Suited For Smile Software</title>
      <link>/industries/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 10:35:13 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/industries/</guid>
      <description>When you partner with Inomial you’re joining some of Asia-Pacific’s leading independent ISPs and telcos. But Inomial’s skill
and years of experience does not end there. Smile’s vendor neutral design, it’s ability to successfully integrate with other
technologies and applications and an extensive feature list allows for immense flexibility. Smile software is well suited for any
industry with a requirement for automatic billing and service management.
Inomial firmly believes that billing as a service is not a one size fits all situation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>