<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on inomial</title>
    <link>http://inomial.tk/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on inomial</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 11:20:32 +0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://inomial.tk/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Linking Help Desk Tickets in Smile Software</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/linking-help-desk-tickets-in-smile/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 11:20:32 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/linking-help-desk-tickets-in-smile/</guid>
      <description>Linking help desk tickets lets you associate&amp;nbsp;tickets that have a similar cause or subject. For example, if a customer has a recurring ADSL problem, you can link the tickets of each instance of the problem together. Linking tickets helps you easily refer to information in other tickets so you can determine common problems or trends or see what actions have already been taken.
Instructions for Linking Tickets in Smile Software To link tickets, click the Add a comment… button in a ticket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smile News – May 2017</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-newsmay-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 11:39:49 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-newsmay-2017/</guid>
      <description>Inomial and DGIT Systems win TMForum Catalyst Award for Outstanding Open Architecture and API Design
We were excited to be a Catalyst participant at the recent TMForum Live! 2017 event in Nice, France. TMForum catalysts are rapid fire, member-driven, proof-of-concept projects which both inform and leverage TM Forum best practices and standards, connecting service providers, technology suppliers, and global enterprises to create truly thought-leading and innovative solutions to industry challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smile News – April 2017</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-newsapril-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 12:04:39 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-newsapril-2017/</guid>
      <description>Farewell from Royce
After what feels like forever Royce Ausburn is leaving Inomial. He and Louise are relocating to the USA where he will take up a new programming role. He has&amp;nbsp;worked with most, if not all, of our users over the years and has been instrumental in the development of Smile.
Whilst we are very sad to see him go, we’re also very excited for the international adventure ahead for him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smile News March 2017</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-news-march-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 10:53:42 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-news-march-2017/</guid>
      <description>docs.inomial.com
Inomial is happy to announce that our documentation is now accessible in HTML. You will also no longer need to log in for access.
Web help versions of our major guides – the User, Configuration and Developer Guides – are now available with more to follow. Each document has a powerful search function to help you find any topic.
Go to&amp;nbsp;docs.inomial.com 
    Inomial at Telecoms World Asia 2017</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smile News February 2017</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-news-february-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 10:57:10 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-news-february-2017/</guid>
      <description>Inomial at NZNOG
Inomial began 2017 as a sponsor and attendee at NZNOG in Tauranga, New Zealand. It was a well organised exhibition and conference attended by a large number of Internet Services Providers from all over New Zealand. Our Kiwi colleagues gave us a warm reception and we valued the opportunity to meet with some of their countries network operators.

(Photo credit&amp;nbsp;GoWireless NZ)     NZNOG Raspberry Pi 3 winners</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smile 6 Replaces Ultrafast Fibres Old Billing System 56 Days</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-6-replaces-ultrafast-fibres-old-billing-system-56-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 11:13:08 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-6-replaces-ultrafast-fibres-old-billing-system-56-days/</guid>
      <description>Our biggest customer success story of the year was the deployment of our cloud product, Smile Pro, into&amp;nbsp;Ultrafast Fibre. UFF is one of New Zealand’s largest fibre broadband wholesalers.
We’re super proud of our achievements with UFF. Following the signing of the Smile contract, the first successful billing cycle run took just&amp;nbsp;56 days – “soup to nuts”&amp;nbsp;– a huge effort for both companies. Compared to their previous billing platform, we’ve reduced the invoice processing time by&amp;nbsp;144 hours per month, allowed UFF to increase order throughput to&amp;nbsp;7,000 orders per month&amp;nbsp;(the majority of which are new services added to Smile), we’ve helped&amp;nbsp;increase staff productivity by 255%,&amp;nbsp;and UFF has been able to reduce both billing and human errors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smile News December 2016</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-news-december-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 10:59:13 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-news-december-2016/</guid>
      <description>Reflections on 2016
December is a great time to enjoy a look back at the year that was. For Inomial, 2016 was a year of big changes.
For me personally, the most important event of the year was having my long time mentor, Ian Fry, join Inomial as CEO. After Ian took over day to day responsibilities for the business back in February, I’ve been able to return to what I love — being a huge geek.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inomial Dgit Systems Partnership</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/inomial-dgit-systems-partnership/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 10:08:19 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/inomial-dgit-systems-partnership/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp;
SINGAPORE – December 6, 2016 – TM Forum Asia – DGIT Systems and Inomial have today announced a partnership to deliver converged billing and fulfilment solutions to the global telecommunications market.
This landmark partnership between two of Australia’s leading independent telecommunication software vendors aims to redefine the way carriers and ISPs order, fulfil and bill their customers, while extending DGIT’s renowned alignment with TM Forum principles and APIs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smile News November 2016</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-news-november-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2016 11:28:57 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-news-november-2016/</guid>
      <description>Inomial at NZNOG 2017
Inomial are an event sponsor of the 2017 New Zealand Network Operators Group (NZNOG) conference in Tauranga. Come and visit our stand if you’re attending in January, and check out the Raspberry Pi’s that we’ll be giving away to some lucky visitors.

Exciting things are happening with Inomial in New Zealand. We’ll be announcing our two most recent NZ customers shortly!    Configuring usage alerts for data services in Smile</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas 2017 New Year Office Arrangements</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/christmas-2017-new-year-office-arrangements/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2016 11:31:39 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/christmas-2017-new-year-office-arrangements/</guid>
      <description>In preparation for the Christmas and New Year break please note the following:
   Office closure
Our offices will be closed over the Christmas – New Year period from&amp;nbsp;Monday&amp;nbsp;26th December through to Monday 2nd January 2017.
We will be open again on&amp;nbsp;Tuesday 3rd January 2017.
    Support
Emergency support will remain available for any business critical issues during this period. In the event this is required please call +61 3 9663 3554 and listen to the recorded message.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smile News October</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-news-october/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2016 11:33:03 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-news-october/</guid>
      <description>Configuring payment declined&amp;nbsp;alerts in Smile
Smile software can be configured to send an alert to an account holder when a payment has been declined. To create a payment declined alert in Smile multiple components need to be defined and then brought together or linked. The&amp;nbsp;Payment Declined Alert – Quick Reference Guide&amp;nbsp;steps you through an example sequence to create an emailed alert.Contact Inomial support if you require a&amp;nbsp;Document Library&amp;nbsp;logon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smile News September</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-news-september/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2016 11:35:45 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-news-september/</guid>
      <description>Inomial Document Library
Smile billing&amp;nbsp;provides access to a library of almost 40 documents including:
 quick reference and format guides user guides and manuals administrator documentation detailed API documentation and much more  Keep an eye out for Smile 6 documents that will be added in the coming months.
Contact Inomial&amp;nbsp;support&amp;nbsp;if you require a&amp;nbsp;Document Library&amp;nbsp;username and password. One often overlooked, yet greatly appreciated, aspect of our service is the level of systems monitoring we do on your behalf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smile News August</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-news-august/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2016 11:37:27 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-news-august/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp;
   Smile billing system monitoring and support
One often overlooked, yet greatly appreciated, aspect of our service is the level of systems monitoring we do on your behalf. In particular, monitoring of service usage&amp;nbsp;like CDRs or similar.
When you create a service in Smile&amp;nbsp;software and begin receiving a data feed from your supplier, even if you are only testing, our monitoring tools recognise both the new service and recent activity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smile System Monitoring And Support</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-system-monitoring-and-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2016 11:40:33 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-system-monitoring-and-support/</guid>
      <description>As a company we take great pride in the quality of service we provide our customers. The Inomial team genuinely cares about the quality of the experience you have with us. We are particularly proud of the attention to detail which extends through all of our interactions with you – from under-the-hood architecture and implementation of technical solutions through to our exchanges&amp;nbsp;with you from our sales, deployment and support departments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smile News – July 2016</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-news-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2016 11:41:51 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-news-8/</guid>
      <description>Smile and LTE EPC launch at Telecom Fiji
Inomial recently teamed up with&amp;nbsp;OASIS Systems, a leading Australian telecommunication solutions provider, to deliver a carrier-grade diameter gateway between&amp;nbsp;Telecom Fiji‘s new LTE EPC and Smile.
Smile software&amp;nbsp;already provides the subscriber and policy management engine for TFL’s ADSL, CDMA and WiFi service offerings. This project was delivered within record time, allowing TFL to offer LTE data services to their customers and remain competitive following infrastructure damage caused by cyclone earlier this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smile News – June 2016</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-news-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2016 11:43:57 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-news-7/</guid>
      <description>Smile 6 in production
We’re excited to announce that Inomial customer&amp;nbsp;MeshTelco&amp;nbsp;has become our first customer to enter production with Smile 6. Smile 6 includes a brand new user interface, a new analytics application, single sign-on, and a host of under-the-hood features.
   “At Mesh, we believe in a simplistic approach to communication and technology. We are a team of passionate and dedicated people, delivering software and hardware solutions to our customers,” says Adam Delon, MeshTelco CEO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Office Locations In Smile</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/office-locations-in-smile/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 11:47:18 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/office-locations-in-smile/</guid>
      <description>New in Smile 6 are office locations. Office locations are a list of physical locations. These locations identify the location of a Smile software operator or a sale location of an invoice line item.
Smile operator location A Smile operator’s location is set in their operator account profile. The selected location will be used as the default when the operator creates invoice line items.
Capabilities determine if an operator can change their default location or the location of other operators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smile News – May 2016</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-news-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 11:50:32 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-news-6/</guid>
      <description>Invoice grouping in Smile
In Smile software, invoice grouping is a way of specifying how charge items are displayed on an invoice. Invoice grouping can be used to display bundle charges on an invoice without itemising the individual charges that apply to the bundle.&amp;nbsp;Charge items can be displayed grouped together or rolled up into one line entry.
More information      CommunicAsia2016
Inomial is again exhibiting at&amp;nbsp;CommunicAsia, which will be held in Singapore, May 31 – June 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Invoice Grouping In Smile</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/invoice-grouping-in-smile/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 11:52:58 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/invoice-grouping-in-smile/</guid>
      <description>In Smile billing, invoice grouping is a way of specifying how charge items are displayed on an invoice. Invoice grouping can be used to display bundle charges on an invoice without itemising the individual charges that apply to the bundle.
Charge type behaviours Charge items can be displayed grouped together or rolled up into one line item.
 Group –&amp;nbsp;Charges are still displayed individually on an invoice, but charges of the same charge type are displayed grouped together on the page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smile News – April 2016</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-news-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2016 11:55:21 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-news-5/</guid>
      <description>Inomial on tour
Currently Inomial is exhibiting at the&amp;nbsp;PCTA Convention 2016&amp;nbsp;in Manila. We’ll be at booth 79 until April 15.&amp;nbsp;Then from April 25-29&amp;nbsp;we will be exhibiting at the&amp;nbsp;PITA 20th AGM &amp;amp; Annual Telecommunications Conference&amp;nbsp;in&amp;nbsp;Tahiti.
If you’re attending either of these conferences come and say hello!
             Smile 6
The release of Smile 6 is nearing. We’ve put a lot of effort into Analytics – our new reporting interface, so you can produce fast and flexible reports.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smile News – February 2016</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-news-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2016 11:56:46 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-news-4/</guid>
      <description>Ian Fry starts as Inomial’s CEO
Ian Fry has taken on the role of Chief Executive Officer of Inomial. Ian has been involved with Inomial for a number of years providing expert guidance. He will now provide strategic management and direction in a full-time role. His focus is on the profitability and growth of Inomial.
Ian has considerable experience and knowledge of the ICT industry, with a particular focus on telecommunications and internet delivery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ian Fry Inomials New Ceo</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/ian-fry-inomials-new-ceo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 11:58:29 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/ian-fry-inomials-new-ceo/</guid>
      <description>Ian Fry today took up the role of Chief Executive Officer of Inomial.
Ian has been involved with Inomial for a number of years providing expert guidance. He will now provide strategic management and direction in a full-time role. His focus is on the profitability and growth of Inomial.
Ian has considerable experience and knowledge of the ICT industry, with a particular focus on telecommunications and internet delivery. Most recently he was the executive officer of Ballarat ICT where he lead innovation, advocacy and education of digital enterprise and broadband technologies across the Ballarat region.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inomial at PTC ’16</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/inomial-at-ptc16/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2016 11:59:36 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/inomial-at-ptc16/</guid>
      <description>Inomial is exhibiting at PTC ’16 this week. If you’re also in Hawaii drop by our booth and talk to Richard Giuliano and Royce Ausburn about Subscription Automation and Revenue Assurance.


&amp;nbsp;

17–20 January 2016 | Honolulu, Hawaii
Hilton Hawaiian Village® Waikiki Beach ResortThe Pacific Telecommunications Council‘s annual conference is the Asia-Pacific’s premier telecommunications event. Now in its 38th year, the annual conference is a strategic springboard for the global telecommunications industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smile News – December 2015</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-news-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 12:02:00 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-news-3/</guid>
      <description>Additional invoice document fields
Additional invoice document fields have been added to Smile software stationery for more flexible and informative documents. The previously inconsistent field ‘payment since last invoice date’ also now works correctly.&amp;nbsp;Available from Smile 5.4.25 new fields include:
 adjustments/surcharges with/without GST charges and GST since last invoice ‘account trading name’ (added to multiple document types)      Notification support in credit control</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas And New Year Office Arrangements</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/christmas-and-new-year-office-arrangements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2015 12:03:19 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/christmas-and-new-year-office-arrangements/</guid>
      <description>In preparation for the Christmas and New Year break please note the following:
   Office closure
Our offices will be closed over the Christmas – New Year period from&amp;nbsp;Thursday 24th December (Christmas&amp;nbsp;Eve) through to Sunday 3rd January 2016.
We will be open again on&amp;nbsp;Monday 4th January 2016.
    Support
Emergency support will remain available for any business critical issues during this period. In the event this is required please call +61 3 9663 3554 and listen to the recorded message.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solomon Telekom Complete First Bill Run With Smile</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/solomon-telekom-complete-first-bill-run-with-smile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2015 12:04:14 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/solomon-telekom-complete-first-bill-run-with-smile/</guid>
      <description>A good reason to Smile with recurring billing solution from Inomial.
Today Solomon Telekom completed their first bill run for mobile, fixed and internet services using Smile software, Inomial’s real-time integrated accounting, provisioning, help desk and customer relationship management CRM system.
“We are very excited to help Solomon Telekom achieve this milestone. Not only has our partnership with Solomon Telekom provided a solution to meet their expanding needs, but Smile billing is also adding value for their customers,” said Mark Lillywhite, Inomial’s Managing Director.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smile News – November 2015</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-news-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2015 12:05:52 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-news-2/</guid>
      <description>Charge from/to columns in invoice user interface
Transaction item charge from and to dates are now visible in the Smile software UI when viewing an invoice or any other itemised transaction. Charge dates are also visible on deferred items on accounts. Smile software admins no longer have to rely on charge dates being included on transaction item descriptions that may not be visible in the UI. Available from Smile 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smile News</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 12:09:58 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-news/</guid>
      <description>Responsive credit control
If a customer consistently pays late, Smile software can automatically change the account terms to stricter terms. You can set rules based on how long and how many invoices are overdue, the amount overdue and the action to take. When they become a better paying customer their terms will automatically improve. Coming in Smile software 6.0.
More information     Future billing</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future Billing</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/future-billing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2015 12:12:26 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/future-billing/</guid>
      <description>Many customers will be familiar with the future billing button available at the bottom of a Subscription’s service tab. From Smile 6.0 this can be used to show what charges will be raised on future invoices, but for that subscription only and for non-usage charges only. This is handy for showing the effect of scheduled plan changes, for example, upgrades and downgrades.

When using this function, Smile software used to show the cumulative position for future invoices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automate 2014 Inomial User Conference Wrap Up</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/automate-2014-inomial-user-conference-wrap-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2014 12:15:04 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/automate-2014-inomial-user-conference-wrap-up/</guid>
      <description>We held our inaugural User Conference in Melbourne on June 10 and 11. We think it went well, with attendance of partners from across Australia and the Pacific Islands, so we are keen to share with you what we covered, particularly our plans for the future.
We’d also like to hear more from you and what you need. We took note of your comments during the conference, but you can keep the conversation going with us or each other in our User Forum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smile You Are On Fetch Tv</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-you-are-on-fetch-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 12:23:24 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/smile-you-are-on-fetch-tv/</guid>
      <description>Inomial today announced an agreement to provide telco billing software to Fetch TV for its’ subscription IPTV service.
Inomial was selected to provide robust and flexible end user billing automation for Fetch TV as it grows its direct subscription customer base.
Inomial’s extensive automated billing and revenue&amp;nbsp;management experience is well suited to IPTV markets. For this project, Inomial has developed a high performance, highly available, distributed API which integrates with the Fetch TV systems and content network to enable a complete, resilient end-to-end billing functionality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vaadin early-bird discount registration closing soon!</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/vaadin-early-bird-discount-registration-closing-soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2014 14:49:55 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/vaadin-early-bird-discount-registration-closing-soon/</guid>
      <description>Vaadin Fundamentals (2 days) June 3&amp;nbsp;–&amp;nbsp;4, Melbourne CBD
Advanced Vaadin (2 days) June 5&amp;nbsp;–&amp;nbsp;6, Melbourne CBD
 Sign up 4 weeks before the event and receive a 10% early-bird discount. Sign up for both courses and get the Vaadin Certification Exam for free. Places are limited so register now.  Inomial is excited to announce that Vaadin are bringing their Vaadin Fundamentals and Advanced Vaadin training courses to Melbourne. Vaadin will power the user interface of the next generation of Inomial Smile software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vaadin Training Coming To Melbourne</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/vaadin-training-coming-to-melbourne/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2014 14:51:25 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/vaadin-training-coming-to-melbourne/</guid>
      <description>Inomial is super excited to announce that Vaadin Fundamentals and Advanced Vaadin training is coming to Melbourne this June.
Vaadin Fundamentals June 3 –&amp;nbsp;4, 2014
Advanced Vaadin June 5 –&amp;nbsp;6, 2014
Early bird pricing now available.
Places are limited so register now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Recurring Billing white paper</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/adaptive-recurring-billing-white-paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2013 14:54:06 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/adaptive-recurring-billing-white-paper/</guid>
      <description>Inomial’s Adaptive Recurring Billing automatically manages all types of billing use cases, many of&amp;nbsp;which are very difficult to compute manually. Adaptive Recurring Billing allows your product rules to&amp;nbsp;match your customer, technical and business requirements, reduces billing disputes, and improves cash&amp;nbsp;flow with fewer errors and better assurance.
This flexibility allows your business to generate the correct revenue regardless of the complexity of&amp;nbsp;changes made to the recurring billing configuration of your customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Case Study Fetch Tv</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/case-study-fetch-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2013 14:55:42 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/case-study-fetch-tv/</guid>
      <description>Inomial has signed a major deal with Solomon Islands incumbent Solomon Telekom to provide its billing system for mobile, fixed and Internet services. It’s one of a number of recent deals Inomial has done in the South Pacific this year.
Solomon Telekom selected Inomial’s Smile Revenue Management solution to replace their legacy billing system that was over 15 years old and was more suited to the fixed network environment it had been introduced for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy Mobile Data Sharing With Smile</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/easy-mobile-data-sharing-with-smile/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2013 14:56:36 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/easy-mobile-data-sharing-with-smile/</guid>
      <description>In Smile, it’s easy to create products where multiple devices all draw from a single, shared pool of data and/or call allowances. This style of billing is common in the US market and is catching on in Australia. Smile has supported this feature for many years.
For network operators and layer 2 MVNOs, Smile also supports shared policy management; Smile can automatically apply overage policies (such as traffic shaping, call restriction, or walled gardens) to all of the devices which share a given allowance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inomial Wins Prestigious Acomms Award</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/inomial-wins-prestigious-acomms-award/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2013 14:57:29 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/inomial-wins-prestigious-acomms-award/</guid>
      <description>We’re honoured to have been selected as the winner of the 2013 ACOMMS Awards for SERVICES TO INDUSTRY – PROFESSIONAL SERVICES.
The award was based on the deployment of our forthcoming high performance rating product, BigRating, to a customer site. We’ll have more news about BigRating soon.
“The ACOMM Awards represent the pinnacle of achievement for the Australian communications industry” – Communications Alliance CEO, John Stanton</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are All Billing Cycles Created Equal</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/are-all-billing-cycles-created-equal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2012 14:58:47 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/are-all-billing-cycles-created-equal/</guid>
      <description>A billing cycle dictates when invoices are sent and when they are due, and impacts your cash flow and the utilisation of network resources. Smile supports monthly and anniversary billing cycles, but what’s the difference between the two?
If you use a monthly billing cycle, the invoices for all customers are generated on the same day each month. This is a good option for smaller businesses, because you only need to process the billing run once a month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inomial Brings A Smile To Internodes New Mobile Offering</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/inomial-brings-a-smile-to-internodes-new-mobile-offering/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2012 14:59:52 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/inomial-brings-a-smile-to-internodes-new-mobile-offering/</guid>
      <description>Inomial recently partnered with Internode, one of Australia’s largest telecommunications carriers, to implement Smile as a revenue system for Internode’s new NodeMobile voice offering. Developed by Inomial, Smile helps telcos and ISPs manage their revenue and collections.
Inomial and Internode have created a solution that Internode founder Simon Hackett describes as an “awesome product”. Inomial’s agile development team extended Smile to meet Internode’s requirements, providing a smooth integration into existing systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding The Cloud</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/understanding-the-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2011 15:01:07 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/understanding-the-cloud/</guid>
      <description>I was recently invited by Ballarat ICT to give a talk about “understanding the cloud”. I don’t often speak at this kind of thing and it was great fun to flex my Keynote skills, and some of the research I did for the talk was quite interesting.
Among other things, I made the point that consolidating and sharing IT resources is not at all new; we’ve been doing it since the dawn of the CPU.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newsat Business Results</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/newsat-business-results/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2011 15:02:56 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/newsat-business-results/</guid>
      <description>From July 7 Communications Day: “Satellite firm NewSat has bagged another A$2.35 million in new business contracts across its well-established military, mining, construction and naval stomping grounds. The wins take the company’s total new business haul in FY11 to A$16 million.”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zettagrid Cloud Launch</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/zettagrid-cloud-launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2011 15:02:03 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/zettagrid-cloud-launch/</guid>
      <description>From Communications Day, July 6th: “Australian cloud services provider ZettaGrid has launched its VMware vCloud Connector beta programme to assist customers in managing a hybrid cloud environment.”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telstra Reaches Agreement With Nbnco</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/telstra-reaches-agreement-with-nbnco/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 15:03:59 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/telstra-reaches-agreement-with-nbnco/</guid>
      <description>“The deal between Telstra and NBN Co still needs to be approved by the phone company’s shareholders, but it is not expected to face major investor opposition.”
Read more</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Platform Networks Helping Deploy Greenfield Fibre</title>
      <link>http://inomial.tk/post/platform-networks-helping-deploy-greenfield-fibre/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2011 15:04:53 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://inomial.tk/post/platform-networks-helping-deploy-greenfield-fibre/</guid>
      <description>From&amp;nbsp;itNews:
“…there’s still many opportunities for smaller players to be involved in [the greenfield deployment] market,” Platform Networks managing director David Hooton said.
“We have an agreement with Comverge to assist them in developing their retail service provider channel. We’re doing service delivery, they’re doing the [network] building.”
Platform Networks was recently named the only wholesale-only participant in mainland NBN first release sites, bolstering its NBN credentials.
Hooton said he and Comverge were “very keen to hear from any greenfields developers”.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>